Effective frontend developer with great experience in web development, who has ability to find solution to any issue. Worked with all of the major paradigms in web development, including MVC, MVVM, and Flux. Willing to use skills for building best product.

# **Major skills**

- Excellent javascript knowledge including es6
- Strong HTML/CSS level
- TDD, BDD
- Client-server interaction (AJAX, WebSockets, Longpoll, REST)
- Fast learning

#### Related skills

Backbone, React, Flux, Angular, Mocha, Grunt, Gulp, Webpack, Enb, Git, Mercurial, Node.js, Coffee, Jade, Handlebars, Balsamiq mockups, Mongodb, Nginx, Linux, Docker, Browser extensions.

#### **Education**

National Research University of Electronic Technology, Russia (2007-2011) Bachelor degree in Automation and Control

# **Professional experience**

### Software engineer at letterfriend.com ○ 2015 – Present

Build automated service for handwritten letters sending. Backend: Loopback.io + Nginx + Docker + MongoDB. Frontend: Reactjs + Flux + Baobab.js.

# **Software engineer** $\circ$ 2014 – Present

Developed open source project <u>github.com/bearded-web</u>.

Built a single page application based on React (and Flux) from scratch. Wrote some server-side code on Go language.

# Frontend developer at yandex.com o 2013-2014

Created a new and upgraded an old UI element as part of a large team, using BEM. Improved codebase with linter and set up a CI system for 15+ developers. It reduces the time on code-review by 1/3.

Created a package tool, similar to NPM for inner usage.

### **Senior frontend developer at metabar.ru** o 2012-2013

Built rich systems (statistics dashboards, admin panels) based on Angular as well as browser extensions (Chrome, IE, Firefox, Opera) based on backbone. Develop part of nodejs statistics aggregator.

Created a powerful framework which allowed fast development of browser extensions.

## Frontend developer at Lakehouse.ru o 2011 - 2012

Built large CRM systems with ExtJS framework. Created a universal architecture that streamlined production.